(Leonard:)That never happened once.
(Raj:)I think the next time I have to speak
to a call center in India...
(Raj:)...I'm going to try using
an American accent.
(Howard:)Why?
(Raj:)Because when I use my regular voice,
I feel like I'm making fun of them.
(Howard:)That's ridiculous. Not to mention,
your American accent is terrible.
(Raj:)Dude, my accent is brilliant.
(Raj:)Hey, my snow-white
American friends, let's put some cow meat...
(Raj:)...on the barbecue and eat it
until we're all obese.
This is what you sound like:
"I think I'm talking in an American accent...
(Howard:)...but it really sounds like
I'm wearing a set of giant dentures."
(Raj:)Sheldon, do I really sound like that?
(Howard:)Tell him he sounds like that.
(Raj:)Sheldon, you okay?
(Sheldon:)It's been three days.
(Sheldon:)Why hasn't Stephen Hawking
played a word?